<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ceeds</title>
    <link>http://ceeds.life/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ceeds</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 13:17:11 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ceeds.life/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Male Guide To A Feminist World</title>
      <link>http://ceeds.life/post/male-guide-to-feminism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 13:17:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceeds.life/post/male-guide-to-feminism/</guid>
      <description>Women are at a disadvantage in comparison to men in today&amp;rsquo;s society. Fact, no argument. Solution: Feminists groups should raise awareness and get society to work towards removing this disadvantage. Problem: As a male, I do not think feminist groups are achieving such things. Rather, I think they are making it harder for male and females to coexist peacefully.
Before I get crucified, I agree in gender equality. I truly believe women should get equal pay to a man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dangers of Nationalism</title>
      <link>http://ceeds.life/post/dangers-of-nationalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 08:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceeds.life/post/dangers-of-nationalism/</guid>
      <description>They climbed inside their boxes. They settled with their trinkets. They neither looked nor learned much more and close their lids up tight.
Once they fastened up their boxes, they smiled there inside and they all thought in their darkness that the world was clear and bright.
Dawud Wharnsby
 Nationalism in its purist form is not wrong; there is nothing wrong with being patriotic about where one comes from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porn Hoarding</title>
      <link>http://ceeds.life/post/porn-hoarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 13:38:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceeds.life/post/porn-hoarding/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not going to lie, I am addicted. Or rather, I was, or maybe I still am. The point is, is that I am a data hoarder. I love to look at hard drives, see 100 TB of space, distributed pools, raid pools; I love it all. What comes with that, is the need to gather and store every source of media I can find. I love browsing through my collection, looking at the variety of movies I can potentially watch; even though I haven&amp;rsquo;t watched a single one, or plan to watch in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War on Torrenting</title>
      <link>http://ceeds.life/post/war-on-torrenting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 00:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceeds.life/post/war-on-torrenting/</guid>
      <description>With the recent shutdown of KickAssTorrents, I often get asked the question &amp;ldquo;Well does this mean torrenting is over? I guess the government has won the war on torrenting?&amp;rdquo;. My response to this question is always &amp;ldquo;possibly, but the war was not won because of the government&amp;rdquo;. In fact, I am not sure if the government stood a chance against torrenters.
You see while it is true, KickAssTorrents has been shut down and the owner of the website could be facing charges, these actions usually have little effect on the swarm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Drops Unlimited Storage</title>
      <link>http://ceeds.life/post/amazon-unlimited/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceeds.life/post/amazon-unlimited/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Cloud was the buzz for about 2 years. Launched in 2015, this plan offered unlimited storage for $60 USD/year; making it the cheapest cloud storage plan on the internet.
That’s correct, Amazon had advertised unlimited storage; and at such an affordable price, many peopled had signed up and began using this amazing service.
A large fraction of these users had used this service to upload encrypted &amp;ldquo;Linux ISOs&amp;rdquo; at alarming rates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>